Guide to the Frank Moore Papers MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Printed Materials
  - Subseries B: Artist Catalogues
    - Jean Mayodon Ceramiste at La Galerie Landrot, Paris, undated (Box 30, Folder 1168)
    - Mental Illness Illustrated, Yale Medical Library New Haven., 1962 (Box 30, Folder 1169)
    - la Metafora Travata at Galleria Sperone, Rome., 1994 (Box 30, Folder 1170)
    - Joan Mitchell at the Whitney Museum of American Art, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1171)
    - Giorgio Morandi Retrospective 1912-1957 at World House Galleries. (Box 30, Folder 1172)
    - Moti at Debs and Co., 2000 (Box 30, Folder 1173)
    - Nabil Nahas at Sperone Westwater, New York., undated (Box 30, Folder 1174)
    - New York School: The First Generation at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1175)
    - The Norman Fisher Collection at the Jacksonville Art Museum, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 1176)
    - Oskar Schlemmer: Das Triadische Ballett., 1980 (Box 31, Folder 1177)
    - Christian Peltenburg-Brechneff: Mountain and Sea. inscribed, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 1178)
    - Filippo de Pisis at Galleria Philippe Daverio., 1980 (Box 31, Folder 1179)
    - de Pisis, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1180)
    - Filippo de Pisis at Galleriea Gian Ferrari, Arte Moderna., 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1181)
    - Photographs: Sotheby's auction., 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1182)
    - Donald Richie: Nudes., 1997 (Box 31, Folder 1183)
    - Alberto Saviinino: Musician, Writer and Painter at Paolo Baldacci Gallery, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1184)
    - The Seascpae: Avery and the European Masters at Borgenicht Gallery New York., 1976 (Box 31, Folder 1185)
    - Beverly Semmes: Not Here at the Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 1187)
    - Dean Smith: Drawings at Christopher Grimes Gallery, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 1188)
    - Soutine at Gallerie Yoshii, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1189)
    - Speedy Graphito: Dou venons-nous?, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1190)
    - Southerland: Bees., 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1191)
    - Ten Americans: masters of Watercolor at Andrew Crispo Gallery, New York., 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1192)
    - Fred Tomaselli at James Cohan Gallery, New York. Inscribed, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 1193)
    - Transcend AIDS: Work by Los Angeles Artists with HIV/AIDS., 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1194)
    - Cy Twombly: Paintings and Draawings at the Milwaukee Art Center., 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1195)
    - Uprising: Videotapes on the Palestinain Resistance, undated (Box 31, Folder 1196)
    - The Collection of Gianni Versace: Sotheby's Auction Catalogue., 2001 (Box 31, Folder 1197)
    - Vorticism and its Allies, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1198)
    - Andrew Wyeth. organized by Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts at the Whitney Museum of American Art, New York., 1967 (Box 31, Folder 1199)
  - Subseries C: Periodicals
    - AIDS Treatment News #190, undated (Box 31, Folder 1200)
    - AIDS Treatment News #197 April 15, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1201)
    - American Art and Antiques, november-December 1978 (Box 31, Folder 1202)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research. Summer 1990 Report. (Box 31, Folder 1203)
    - Art Forum, April 1996 (Box 31, Folder 1204)
    - The Arts. February 1931. (Box 31, Folder 1205)
    - C: International contemporary Art. issue number 62, May-August 1999 (Box 31, Folder 1206)
    - Casper the Friendly Ghost. Comic. August 1982, #223 (Box 31, Folder 1207)
    - Christopher Street., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 1208)
    - Digraphe #62, June 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1209)
    - Gai havdo Pied #124, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 1211)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis Newsletter. 8:2 (March 1994) (Box 31, Folder 1212)
    - Glass #46 (Winter 1991-1992) (Box 31, Folder 1213)
    - Innovations [lettering artists], 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1214)
    - Iranian Institute Bulletin 5:4, Mural Paintings from the Cave Temples of India., 1942 (Box 31, Folder 1215)
    - Th Lambda Update 10:2 (Winter 1992), 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1216)
    - New York Times Magazine (10 November 1996) (Box 31, Folder 1220)
    - The Poetry Project volume 155 (December/January 1994-1995) (Box 31, Folder 1221)
    - School of Visual Arts Almuni Magazine. Illustration issue. Winter 2002. (Box 30, Folder 1222)
    - The Sewanee Reveiw 87:4 (Fall 1979) (Box 31, Folder 1223)
    - Shiney International (Spring 1986) (Box 31, Folder 1224)
    - Soceity of Scribes, LTD. Journal. 1:3, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 1225)
    - TAG Line [Treatment Action Group] 8:6 (July-August 2001) (Box 31, Folder 1226)
    - Tricycle: The Buddist Review (Spring 1992) (Box 31, Folder 1227)
    - White Crane: Journal for the exploration of gay men's spirituality. #16, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1228)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous
    - Air France Concorde Menu, undated (Box 31, Folder 1234)
    - America Fashion Awards at Avery Fisher, Thursday June 15, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 1234A)
    - Inflight Movie Program: The Silent One, undated (Box 31, Folder 1237)
    - Kiss the Children Goodbye: The Real Meaning of Nuclear War. A project of Women Strike for Peace., undated (Box 31, Folder 1238)
    - MAC gift certificate for fifty dollars, undated (Box 31, Folder 1239)
    - Menu for Chanterelle for January 22- February 17 1996, with printed cyanotype on cover by John Dugdale (Box 31, Folder 1240)
  - Subseries E: Books
    - Afghan Trucks, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 1244)
    - AIDS Treatment News Vol. 2 edited by John S. James, Denny Smith, Michelle Roland, and Laura Thomas., 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 1245)
    - AIDS Treatment News Vol. 3 edited by John S. James, 1991-1993 (Box 32, Folder 1246)
    - Alloway, Lawrence American Pop Art, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 1248)
    - Ashbery, John and Thomas B. Hess. Painterly Painting, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 1249)
    - Awakawa, Yasuichi Zen Painting, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 1251)
    - Ballard, Ernest Days in My Garden, 1919 (Box 32, Folder 1252)
    - Barlow, T.D. Woodcuts of Albrecht Durer, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 1253)
    - Baudelaire, Charles Les Fleurs du Mal, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 1254)
    - Beary, Kevin. Florentine Locutions: a study of blasphemous and obscene expressions in Florentine Italian, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 1255)
    - Benjamin, Walter Charles Baudelaire: A Lyric Poet in the Era of High Capitalism, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 1256)
    - Bergson, Henri Creative Evolution, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 1257)
    - Between Street and Mirror: The Drawings of James Ensor, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 1258)
    - Joseph Beuys: Heiner Stachelhaus translated by David Britt, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1259)
    - The Biophilia Hypothesis Edited by Stephen R. Kellert and Edward O. Wilson, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1260)
    - Bible Revised Standared Version, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 1261)
    - Blair, Les Jest Tawk: a country dictionary spiced with country sayins., 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1262)
    - Bosman, Richard and Ted Greenwald Exit the Face, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 1263)
    - Boswell, John Christianity, Social Tolerance and Homosexuality. Drawing in back cover, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 1264)
    - Brambila, Rosa Sala de Teotihuacan, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 1265)
    - Buber, Martin I and Thou, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 1267)
    - Burchfield, Charles The Charles Rand Penney Collection of Works., 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1268)
    - Burke, Edmund Reflections on the Revolution in France, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 1269)
    - Callaway, C. Wayne and Catherine Whitney Surviving with AIDS, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1270)
    - Caractere Noel, undated (Box 33, Folder 1271)
    - Carli, Enzo The Maesta duccio de Buoninsegna, undated (Box 33, Folder 1272)
    - Carlisle, Lilian Baker Hat Boxes and Dandboxes at Shelburne Museum, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 1273)
    - Cassirer, Ernst The Philosophy of the Enlightenment, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 1274)
    - Carnegie, Dale How to Win Friends and Influence People, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 1275)
    - Catullo, Luciano The Ancient Roman Villa of Casale at Piazza Armerina: Past and Present, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1276)
    - Charbonnel Encres D'Imprimerie, undated (Box 33, Folder 1277)
    - Coleridge, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 1278)
    - CONASIDA Preguntas y Respuestas sobre SIDA del Personal de Salud, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1279)
    - Cunault, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1280)
    - Debreczeny, Paul Alexander Pushkin: Complete Prose Fiction., 1983 (Box 34, Folder 1284)
    - Deitcher, David Dear Friends: American Photographs of Men Together 1840-1918. annotated, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 1285)
    - Delevoy, Robert Bosch, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1286)
    - Diaz-Bolio, Jose The Geometry of the Maya and their Rattlesnake Art, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 1287)
    - Diego Rivera y la Salud, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 1289)
    - Easton, Robert and Peter Nabokov Native American Architecture, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 1290)
    - Ehrenzweig, Anton The Hidden Order of Art. with annotations, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 1291)
    - Eliade, Mircea Cosmos and History: The Myth of the Eternal Return, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 1292)
    - Eliade, Mircea The Sacred and the Profane: The Nature of Religion., 1961 (Box 34, Folder 1293)
    - Eliot, T.S. Four Quartets., 1971 (Box 34, Folder 1294)
    - Eliot, T.S. The Waste Land and other Poems, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 1295)
    - Ellsworth Kelly, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 1296)
    - Erdman, David V. The Poetry and Prose of William Blake., 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1297)
    - Erlande-Brandenburg, Aiain La Dame a la Licorne, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 1298)
    - Ernst, Max Une Semaine de Bonte, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1299)
    - Feininger, Lyonel The Ruin by the Sea, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1300)
    - Ficke, Arthur Davison Chats on Japanese Prints, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1301)
    - Field, Eugene The Tribune Primer, 1900 (Box 34, Folder 1302)
    - Fifty Years of Modern Art, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 1303)
    - Foucault, Michele The Care of the Self: The History of Sexuality vol. 3, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 1304)
    - Frazer, James George The Golden Bough, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 1305)
    - Friedman, Michael Special Capacity, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 1306)
    - Gallery of Masterpieces: Mona Lisa Gallery of Masterpieces: The Massacre of Chios, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 1307)
    - Gian Enzo Sperone, undated (Box 35, Folder 1308)
    - Gluck, Robert Jack the Modernist, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 1309)
    - Glucksmann, Andre La felure du monde, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1310)
    - Greenly, Mike Chronicle: The Human Side of AIDS, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 1312)
    - Greenwald, Ted Common Sense with annotations, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1313)
    - Grimes, Nancy Jared French's Myths, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 1314)
    - Guide Indicateur des Reus de Paris, undated (Box 35, Folder 1315)
    - Hastreiter, Laurie A photo- typo-graphic essay on water., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1316)
    - Herodotus The Struggle for Greece, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 1317)
    - Hess, Thomas Willem de Kooning, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1318)
    - Hibbert, Christopher The Emperors of China, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 1319)
    - Hockney, David Secret Knowledge with annotations, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 1320)
    - Hockney, David Six Fair Tales, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 1321)
    - Houellebecq, Michel Les particules elementaires, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 1322)
    - Houghton, Norris Great Russian Short Stories, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1323)
    - Hunter, Sam Modern America Op, Pop and the School of Color, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 1324)
    - Huyghe, Rene The Contemporaries, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 1325)
    - Imuthiol in HIV Infection, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1326)
    - Ingholt, Harald Gandharan Art in Pakistan, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 1327)
    - Interchangeable photo-scrap album, undated (Box 36, Folder 1328)
    - Japanese book unknown, undated (Box 36, Folder 1329)
    - Jarman, Derek Queer Edward II, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 1330)
    - Jones, LeRoi The Dead Lecturer, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1331)
    - Jones, Michael Wynn The Cartoon History of the American Revolution, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1332)
    - Jug Bug: The Joy of Juggling, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 1333)
    - Jung, Emma Animus and Anima with annotations, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 1334)
    - Justice, Donald Departures, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 1335)
    - Kandinsky, Wassily Concerning the Spirituality in Art, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 1336)
    - Kapplow, Hal and Bob Reisner Captions Courageous, or, Comments from the Gallery, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 1337)
    - Khayyam, Omar Rubaiyat, undated (Box 37, Folder 1338)
    - Koch, Kenneth Wishes, Lies and Dreams: Teaching Children to Write Poetry, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 1339)
    - Langenscheidt's Universal Dictionary English-Italian and Italian-English, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 1340)
    - Lazarus, Richard Personality 2nd edition, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 1341)
    - Lebensztejn, Jean-Claude Malcolm Morley: Itineraries, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 1342)
    - Lee, Sherman E. The Sketchbooks of Hiroshige, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 1343)
    - Lord, Douglas Vincent Van Gogh Letters to Meile Bernard, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 1344)
    - Love Speaks its Name: Gay and Lesbian Love Poems, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 1345)
    - Lucas, E.V. A Wanderer in Paris, undated (Box 37, Folder 1346)
    - Machiavelli, Niccolo The Prince and The Discourses, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 1347)
    - Mains, Geoff Urban Aboriginals: A Celebration of Leathersexuality, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 1348)
    - Manhattan Observed, undated (Box 37, Folder 1349)
    - Maroc: Costumes, Broderies, Brocarts, undated (Box 37, Folder 1350)
    - Mayer, Ralph The Artist's Handbook of Materials and Techniques, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 1352)
    - McAlester, Virginia and Lee A Field Guide to American Houses, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1353)
    - McDermott and McGough 1936, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 1354)
    - McDonald, Sterling Color Harmony with the McDonald Calibrator, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 1355)
    - Merrill, James A Different Person, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 1356)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art Greek and Roman Art, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1357)
    - Modern Dreams with annotations, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1358)
    - Moholy-nagy, Laszlo The New Vision and Abstract of an Artist, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 1359)
    - Morrisroe, Mark Mark Morrisroe, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 1360)
    - Museum of Modern Art Joseph Cornell, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 1361)
    - Nadeau, Maurice Histoire du Surrealisme, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1362)
    - A New Guide to Rome, undated (Box 38, Folder 1363)
    - New Year Pictures of Weifang, Shantung, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 1364)
    - New York City Landmarks, undated (Box 38, Folder 1365)
    - O'Connor, Flannery The Complete Stories, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 1366)
    - O'Doherty, Brian American Masters: The Voice and the Myth, undated (Box 39, Folder 1367)
    - O'Hara, Frank The Selected Poems of Frank O'Hara, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 1368)
    - Oldenburg, Claes Drawings and Prints, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1369)
    - Ouspensky, P.D. A New Model of the Universe, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 1371)
    - Pickvance, Ronald Van Gogh in Arles, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 1372)
    - de Pisis Opre su carta 1921-1952 with an essay by Francesco Gallo, biography by Claudia Gian Ferrari, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 1373)
    - Plato The Symposium, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 1374)
    - Plato The Symposium of Plato Translated by Suzy Groden, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 1375)
    - Porter: Art in its own terms with annotations, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 1376)
    - Ramakers, Micha Dirty Pictures: Tom of Finland, Masculinity and Homosexuality, advance, uncorrected proof, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 1377)
    - Ricardo, Jack Leathermen Speak Out, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 1378)
    - Ristat, Jean Le Parlement d'amour, undated (Box 39, Folder 1379)
    - Ristelhueber, Sophie Beirut, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 1380)
    - Robertson, Bryan Jackson Pollock, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 1381)
    - Rockman, Alexis Alexis Rockman, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 1382)
    - Rockman, Alexis Evolution, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 1383)
    - de Rola, Stanislas Klossowski The Golden Game, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 1384)
    - Roma, parte 2, undated (Box 40, Folder 1385)
    - Romanesque Catalan Art, undated (Box 40, Folder 1386)
    - Rombauer, Irma and Marion Rombauer Becker The Joy of Cooking with annotations, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 1387)
    - Saunders, E. Dale Mudra: A Study of Symbolic Gestures in Japanese Buddhist Sculpture., 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1388)
    - Savinio, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 1389)
    - Scudiero, Maurizio and David Leiber Depero Futurista dn New York, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 1390)
    - The Science of AIDS, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 1390)
    - Seraullaz, Maurice Degas: Women Dressing, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 1392)
    - Shaw, Albert A Cartoon History of Roosevelt's Career, 1910 (Box 40, Folder 1393)
    - Smith, Bradley Japan: A History in Art, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 1394)
    - Soby,James Thrall The Prints of Paul Klee, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 1395)
    - Souls Grown Deep: African American Vernacular Art of the South [located in oversize box], 2000 (Box 41, Folder 1396)
    - Sparks, Esther Universal Limited, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 1397)
    - Steiner, Jorg and Jorg Muler. The Bear who wanted to be a Bear, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1398)
    - Stein, Gertrude Picasso with annotations, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 1399)
    - Stevens, Wallace The Palm at the End of the Mind, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 1400)
    - Stout, Wesley W. A War Job "Thought Impossible", 1945 (Box 41, Folder 1401)
    - Styron, William Lie down in Darkness, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 1402)
    - Szarkowski, John The Photographer's Eye, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1403)
    - Taschen, Benedikt Cheri Samba Postcard Book, undated (Box 41, Folder 1404)
    - Therrien, Robert Polaroids Drawings, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 1405)
    - Tocqueville, Alexis Democracy in America, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 1406)
    - Tomkins, Calvin Dechamp: a Biography, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 1407)
    - Thompson, Mark Leather-Folk: Radical Sex, People, Politcs and Practice, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 1408)
    - Townsend, Larry The Leatherman's Handbook II, Updated Second Edition, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 1409)
    - A Treasury of Western Folklore, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 1410)
    - Les Tres Riches Heures du duc de Berry, undated (Box 42, Folder 1411)
    - Trinidad, David Three Stories, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 1412)
    - Trollope, Anthony Barchester Towers with annotations, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 1413)
    - Trungpa, Chogyam The Myth of Freedom and the Way of Meditation, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1414)
    - Tsarouchis, Yannis Pientures, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1415)
    - Tyler, Ron Visions of America, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 1416)
    - Valery, Paul Selected Writings, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 1417)
    - Walt Disney's Moving Picture Flip Book, undated (Box 42, Folder 1419)
    - Watson, Steven Strange Bedfellows, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 1420)
    - Wilde, Oscar Plays with annotations, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 1421)
    - Winston, Leyland Queer Dharma: Voices of Gay Buddhists, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 1422)
    - Woolf, Virginia Mrs. Dalloway with annotations, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 1423)
    - Yeats, W.B. Selected Poems and 2 plays, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 1424)
    - Yoganada, Paramahansa The Law of Success, undated (Box 43, Folder 1425)
    - Zhisui, Dr. Li The Private Life of Chairman Mao with annotations, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 1426)
- Series XI: 2023 Accretion, 1983-2001; 1.31 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes
  Arrangement
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  This accretion to the Frank Moore Papers consists of slides of Moore's artwork, photographs, and promotional materials for art exhibitions.
  - Artists with AIDS, undated (Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 9)
  - Bookplate Design, undated (Box Shared Fales 093, Folder 17)
  - Drawings and Postcards (many Visual AIDS), undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 23)
  - Promotional Materials -- Art Exhibitions, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Photographs -- Artwork, undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1983-2002 (Box 71, Folder 3-7, Box 72, Box 73)
- Oversize Materials: Series I, Notebooks
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series I: Notebooks
  - Notebook #4, 1974-1976 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Notebook #9, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Loose Items from Notebook #9, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Notebook #21, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Notebook #26, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Notebook #27, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Loose Items from Notebook #27, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Notebook #28, 1978-1980 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Notebook #31, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Notebook #36, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Notebook #40, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Notebook #41, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Notebook #42, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Notebook #43, 1981-1982 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Notebook #44, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Loose items from Notebook #44, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Notebook #51, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Notebook #59, 1984-1985 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Loose Items from Notebook #59, 1984-1985 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Notebook #73, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Loose Items from Notebook 73, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Notebook #81, 1992-1995 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Notebook #87, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Notebook #96, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Oversize Materials: Series II.A: Frank Moore Clippings, Exhibition Announcements, Press, etc.
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series II.A: Frank Moore Clippings, Exhibition Announcements, Press
  - New York Arts Journal, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - PS1 Poetry Project, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Watercolor Show, 1980-1981 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Collaborative Show with George Negroponte, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Broccoli, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Beast: Animal Imagery in Recent Painting, 1982 (Folder 1 Left)
  - Collaboration with Jim Self at the Kitchen, undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Moulton-Splatter, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Crankhouse, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln Center Exhibit, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Joffrey Ballet, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Certificate of Service, Volunteer Adult Services Administration, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - CFDA: Council of Fashion Designers of America, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Citation for Contribution to SAFE Portfolio, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Slow Art, 1992 (Box 69)
  - Henie-Onstad Kunstesenter Hovikodden, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Cure Project Art Show, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Interview Magazine, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Requested Documentation, 1995 (Box 69)
  - XXX Fruit, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Interview Magazine, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Group Show, includes Frank Moore's The Gambler, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - OUT Magazine Art Calendar, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - "The Art of Being You", Interview Magazine Supplement, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1999 (Box 69)
  - ArtForum, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Interview Magazine, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Frank Moore's Obituary, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Orlando Weekly, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Frank Moore: Between Life and Death, proofs, undated (Folder 4 Left)
  - Genomic Issue(s), 2003 (Box 69)
  - Folder featuring "Wildlife Management Area" and Stretch", undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Hospital sign, undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Yosemite Color Copies, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Oversize Materials: Series II.C: Frank Moore Administrative Files
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series II.C: Frank Moore Administrative Files
  - ArtForum, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Mousepad, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Oversize Materials: Series II.D: Other Artist Art Files
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series II.D: Other Artist Art Files
  - Callahan, Harry, undated (Folder 4 Right)
  - Condo, George, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - de Fazio, undated (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Ford, Walton, undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Frame, Allen, undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Futura 2000, undated (Box 69)
  - Harte, Glynn Boyd, undated (Box 69)
  - Lunch, Lydia, undated (Box 69)